Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ danieleclarissa (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Conscious Sedation

Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS)

Pediatric Advanced Life Support (PALS)

Certifications

CNOR (Certified Nurse Operating Room)

Daniele Clarissa BSN RN, CPN, CNOR

Operating Room RN

San Francisco Bay Area

Summary

I am currently working as a per diem general pediatric operating room and pediatric cardiac surgery RN (circulator and scrub nurse) with 7 years total experience in the operating room, 4 of which I spent as a travel RN. I have some experience at an adult facility, conscious sedation and PACU. I always place my patient first, I adapt and learn quickly, and I am an asset to any team. I am confident I can circulate any surgical case with minimal training and scrub cardiac surgery with cardiopulmonary bypass.

I am not looking to become a travel nurse again anytime soon, as I have decided to stay in the Bay Area.

I am also a landscape photographer (IG: danieleclarissa).

Experience

Stanford Children's Health | Lucile Packard Children's Hospital Stanford

2 years 4 months

Pediatric CV OR RN
October 2018 - Present (1 year 8 months)

Palo Alto, California

Travel Registered Nurse February 2018 - October 2018 (9 months)

Palo Alto, California

UCSF Benioff Children's Hospital San Francisco CVOR RN Per Diem September 2019 - Present (9 months)

Rady Children's Hospital-San Diego

Page 1 of 3

OR Travel Nurse

November 2017 - February 2018 (4 months)

Greater San Diego Area

The Pacific Crest Trail 2017 PCT Thru-Hiker

March 2017 - September 2017 (7 months)

Mexico to Canada

In April of 2017, I will be hiking all 2,659 miles of the Pacific Crest Trail! Click on the link below, to support the PCTA!

Seattle Children's Travel Nurse Pediatric OR April 2016 - March 2017 (1 year) Seattle, Washington

American Mobile Healthcare
Travel Nurse Pediatric OR
September 2015 - March 2017 (1 year 7 months)

Shriners Hospitals for Children - Portland Travel OR Registered Nurse October 2015 - March 2016 (6 months) Portland, Oregon

Aya Healthcare
Travel Nurse
January 2015 - September 2015 (9 months)

Texas Children's Hospital Travel OR Registered Nurse January 2015 - May 2015 (5 months) Houston, Texas

Miami Children's Health System Registered Nurse January 2014 - January 2015 (1 year 1 month)

Riley Children's Hospital Registered Nurse

Miami/Fort Lauderdale Area

January 2013 - January 2014 (1 year 1 month)

Indianapolis, Indiana Area

Education

Indiana University Kokomo
Bachelor of Science (BS), Registered Nursing/Registered
Nurse · (2009 - 2012)